Kamilzhan Irismetov, Golang Developer

Almaty, Kazakhstan | +7 701 204 7070 | mustan989@outlook.com | linkedin.com/in/mustan989

Summary

Golang developer with 2+ years of professional experience in back-end development.

Have experience working independently and in teams of up to 30 people including mentoring and onboarding. Team player as good as an autonomous unit.

Willing to join the team of professionals to build services and platforms that make the world better.

Experience

Golang Developer, Kaspi.KZ, Feb 2022 - Present

- · Developing back-end services for Kaspi Contact Center and CRM system
- Working on internal projects: Database Privilege Manager, Device Location Service, etc.
- Documenting service specifications with Swagger and Confluence
- Implementing code style and commit convention

Stack: Go, HTTP, WebSocket, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Asterisk, Kamailio, RTP, WebRTC

Golang Developer, Sber KZ, Jul 2021 - Feb 2022

- Developed microservices in Golang for Decision Maker, loan approving system
- · Worked on Sber Travel, ticket search and booking service
- Integrated services with State Revenue Committee
- · Participated in code review
- · Mentored three junior developers

Stack: Go, HTTP, Echo, PostgreSQL, Kafka, Docker, Kubernetes, Helm, Jaeger, Prometheus, ElasticSearch, Swagger

Site Reliability Engineer, Sber KZ, Feb 2020 - Jun 2021

- Improved CI/CD pipelines
- · Reduced issues count and SLA time
- Developed and supported IBM Service Bus, participated in service integrations
- · Achieved department's 2020 The Best Employee award

Stack: IBM Integration Bus, IBM MQ, ESQL, ElasticSearch, Kibana, Groovy, Jenkins, Nexus, Jira, Confluence

Education

Satbayev University, Jun 2024

M.S. in Software Engineering, Institute of Information and Telecommunication Technologies

Satbayev University, Jun 2022

B.S. in Computer Science and Software, Institute of Information and Telecommunication Technologies

South Kazakhstan Polytechnic College, Mar 2018

A.S. in Computer Science and Software, Faculty of Electronics and Information Technologies

Languages